...15 minutes out,
we're still focusing.
Can someone get me
the drop count?
Okay. Good to go.
We've got 60%.
Copy that.
We're doing a runner.
Make sure Paper Boi...
And could you get rid of
all the ginger ale in there?
Why?
We asked for "ginger beer,"
not "ginger ale."
Okay, I'm on it.
Eyes on Paper Boi?
Guys, eyes on Paper Boi?
Niggas. Man...
The hell is-- Is that a map?
Uh, this is
an original blueprint
of the building we're in.
There's about f-four...
five rooms
that I think are not on file.
I smell adventure.
Yes.
Nigga, why you even-- Never
mind, man. I ain't doing it.
Oh, man, they say this place
is, like, haunted.
There's a lot of creepy,
unexplained events.
Look, as long as it ain't
another Milwaukee,
man, I'm cool.
Mm. Are you talking
about the raid?
I told you, man,
that was a ghost I saw.
- Nigga, that was
your reflection.
- Hey, man.
- Hey, what's going on?
Yo, Al, Al, you trying to hit
a strip club after the show?
- Oh, no!
- A strip club? Hell no.
- No more European strip clubs,
all right, man?
- I heard that.
It's 100 pounds to get in,
and, uh,
we don't have any titties.
Sprinkle me, milord.
- Sprinkle me.
- Oh, please, make it rain
all over me.
- Make it rain.
- Look at me trying
to clap my ass together...
- Make it rain.
...but I can't find it, so...
Is it hot?
Meet and greet.
The kid from
the Dream Foundation.
For sure, man. All right.
- Hey, what's going on,
little man?
- Hello.
This is Marvy.
- What's that?
- Our evening plans.
- Hi.
- One minute.
It's me again.
You're gonna be seeing a lot
of me. I'm gonna be in and out.
Yeah, I know, I know,
I just need to check, you know?
It's my job.
- Okay. You're good to go.
- Thanks.
Sorry, guys.
Uh, where were we? Um...
Yeah, check the barricade,
no flash photography
for the first three songs.
I'm seeing a lot of people
walking around here;
make sure people can't just
walk in on him...
Hold that up.
Oh, there you go.
Hey, guys. Hope you enjoyed
your time with Paper Boi,
but, uh, he needs to get ready
for the show.
There's a man outside
who'll escort you to your seats.
You want
to take this with you?
All right. There you go.
All right,
y'all take it easy, man.
All right.
- Show in 30.
- All right.
- Hey, you got my, um...
- Here you go.
Cool.
Oh, man,
can you get me a...
Yeah, there's a ginger beer
on stage.
It's right next to your water.
You were saying you were feeling
"musty" on the way over here,
that means you're dehydrated.
You should really drink
more water, but, yeah,
the ginger beer's there.
Okay.
Hey, man, how you been?
- Huh?
- How you been, man?
Oh.
Good, good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Man, 'cause...
...you seem busy
all the time, bruh.
Yeah.
But busy's good, you know?
Yeah. Yep.
All right, guys.
Guys, I'm getting talkback
at the front of house.
Can you check the patch?
Turn the mic off.
- cheering)
Paper Boi! Paper Boi!
- All right, give it up.
- All right, all right,
all right.
Rap gods, for I am not
accustomed to prayer,
bear with me.
I'd like to thank you
for every life
that's here with me.
- You shall bestow...
- Hell yeah.
- ...Alfred with the energy
on to show.
- Yeah, man. Yeah!
- Let's go!
- All right, shake.
- He's here!
Paper Boi! Come on!
Whoo! Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Hey!
Get the fuck off the stage.
Paper Boi!
Paper Boi! Paper Boi!
Man, who the fuck is that?
We'll deal with it
after the show.
- Start the show?
- Good luck.
I did not know you were poppin'
like that in Budapest.
Might have to add this stop
to the next tour.
What y'all looking for?
Just tried again.
Went to voice mail.
- Fucking phone?
- Yeah.
Man, we need
to hurry up and find this.
We still have
our map adventure to go on.
Hey, man, I got back from
my set, my shit was gone.
The one in the gold case?
When was the last time
you had it?
Man, it was out on the dock,
and then, uh...
I came back in for the meet
and greet with that cancer kid.
- And you didn't have it after?
- No, man.
No, man.
He wouldn't do that.
There was something weird
about that kid, man.
Uh, wait,
that dude is a fan, man.
Imagine if you had your
favorite celebrity phone.
Shit, man! Is he still here?
Hold on.
Yeah, does anybody
have eyes on the, uh,
VIPs from the meet and greet?
I think he's currently
being rushed
out of the building.
- Why?
- The paramedics were called in.
He said he was having
a cancer attack.
Cancer att... No.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, man, wa--
I'm telling you,
if we just stick to...
- Not now, man, not now.
- Ah... damn.
Hey, hey!
- I need to talk to that kid.
- What?
No.
If it is for Paper Boi,
I want to help.
- Marvy, I don't think...
- Mom.
I need to do this.
What does Paper Boi need?
Um...
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Get away from my son!
Boo!
Sorry. Thought he had a phone,
thought he had a phone.
Hey, you find him?
- He didn't take it.
- Man, how you know
he ain't take it?
- What you do? You just ask...
- Believe me, he didn't have it.
I could've told you
that boy didn't take that phone.
Nigga, you the one... Whatever.
Man, fuck, man.
I need that phone, Earn.
It's just a phone, man.
Look, I...
I can have a runner get one
in the morning for you.
Man, shit.
I know this is
a very memorial vibe,
but, uh, we can make
the whole situation
a little bit better
if we just...
Hey, look, it ain't even
about the phone, man.
It's about the shit
that's on the phone.
- iCloud?
- No, we don't do iCloud.
No, yeah, exactly.
I'd have my shit backed up, too,
if it wasn't for
conspiracy Jones over here.
Who could've taken that phone?
What about that runner guy?
I think he was a runner, right?
That kid in the blue jacket?
The super unprofessional
stage manager.
That nigga that
was on the stage?
Oh, I thought that dude
was the caterer.
Oh, hey, buds.
Good gig.
You ready to settle up?
Yeah, Folk, soon. Um, can I talk
to that stage manager?
The stage manager?
He wasn't here today.
I was covering for him.
Then who was that guy?
What guy?
The guy who was...
He had crazy brown hair,
he was kind of young,
he was going around
asking people stuff...
He had a blue jacket.
- Oh, you talking about Wiley?
- Who?
Yeah, Wi--
Blue jacket, brown hair.
Yeah, Wiley. That's my nephew.
- Your nephew?
- Yeah.
He was here for a meeting
with the rigger about a job.
Okay, well, Al had his phone
stolen. We need to talk to him.
Really? That's very unfortunate.
You don't think
Wiley took it, do you?
Well, he was backstage
all night.
Eh... I'm sure
he didn't take it.
Well, I'm not saying he did,
I'm just saying
we'd like to talk to him.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Well... text him.
Can you text him?
I don't have his number.
You don't have
your nephew's phone number?
No.
I have his father's number, but
it is too late to call him now.
Well, it's an emergency.
An artist at your venue
had something stolen.
The rigger has his number.
I will get the number
from the rigger.
Okay, I'll come with you.
- What, you want it now?
- Yes.
Old boy doesn't even work here.
- Man, he don't work--
Then how the fuck...
- He's Folk's nephew.
He was here for an interview,
but he left.
This is his resume.
We got his info.
Man, call this fucker right now.
Hell yeah, and put that shit
on speakerphone, man.
- Shit.
Hello?
Hey, uh, is this Wiley?
Uh, as far as I know.
Hi, this is, uh, Earn,
Paper Boi's manager.
We spoke earlier today
at the show.
Show?
The-the Paper Boi concert.
Oh...
Uh, the rap presentation.
Yes. How can I help you?
Yeah, well, you disappeared.
Didn't you want
to meet Paper Boi?
Yeah, but he seemed, uh, busy.
Yeah, busy.
Well, he wanted to meet you.
We wanted to know if you,
you know, live near the venue.
You're, uh, you're calling
up fans randomly
to invite them to meet you.
- I feel like there's
an ulterior motive.
- No, no...
Listen, man, we're done
playing with you, yeah?
Do you know who you're
fucking with?
- Socks.
- Keep playing
with Team Paper Boi, yeah,
we're plugged in down here, man.
Mob shit. Yeah?
Like I'm the white
Liam Neeson, bruv.
I will track you down,
and I will fucking bury you
if you're not back here
in 15 minutes, phone in hand!
Bring the fucking phone back,
or we'll fucking kill you!
What is this? What the fuck
is wrong with you, nigga?
Hey, yo, man, hey.
What's going on, man?
It's Paper Boi right here.
We ain't gonna kill you, man.
We just, we just want to talk.
That man said
you were going to kill me.
Yeah, I know. I know, I know,
but he, uh, he was
just playing, man. Hey,
how about this, man, you-- if
you far-- Are you far from here?
Whatever. Hey, man,
come back to the venue,
I'll be here to meet you.
Call your uncle.
I swear it's legit, for real.
- Wiley?
- What the hell, Socks?
- Look, I'm sorry, man.
He's full of shit.
He's got that phone.
Yeah. We knew that,
but we need him
to come back here.
- White Liam Neeson?
- Like, what the fu--
That don't even make
no fucking sense, Socks, huh?
Are you thinking
of Samuel L. Jackson?
- Yeah, who are you
thinking about, man?
- What's wrong with you?
Fucking Liam Neeson's
already fucking white!
This is not how my night
was supposed to go, man.
Yeah.
Mine, either.
Yo, he came back.
Oh, shit.
- God!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You stay out here, okay?
You too hot, all right?
Uh, yeah.
Breathe.
Yeah, it's cool,
it's cool, it's cool.
Fuck!
H-Hello.
Hi.
How... how are you guys
enjoying Budapest?
Let's just get to the point.
You didn't happen to see a phone
while you were backstage
- all day, did you?
- What kind of phone, iPhone?
- Uh, Samsung?
- Doesn't matter...
Dawg, you find a phone or not?
No.
No, I didn't.
You know there's a "find
my phone" app that could--
- Yeah, that could help.
- No, no, no,
we don't use that.
That's how they track us,
you know better than that.
- Come on now.
- Ah.
Why were you backstage all day?
Oh, I was waiting
for my interview.
Then why'd you come back?
I thought about what you said.
I didn't want to miss
a chance to meet...
...Paper Boi.
I'm a long-time admirer of his.
Well, Paper Boi has
a really early flight tomorrow.
And if you know
where his phone is,
it'd be really helpful.
Is there something special
about this phone?
Is that why you said you were
going to kill me?
- What?
N-No, we didn't say that.
We... we're not gonna hurt you.
If I died today,
people will assume you did it,
I think.
They-the will.
Nobody's gonna die, Wiley.
We all have to die sometime.
You know that?
Maybe my end...
...should come
at the hands of Paper Boi.
This is funny.
Meeting you like this,
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Trust me, ain't nobody
dreaming this, dawg.
What do you dream of?
Box-top Chevys?
Or kissing the thorn on a rose?
Oh, it's sweet, but it hurts.
It'd make you never want
to trust...
...anything too beautiful
again.
Out.
Listen, he's just scared.
He's only 19.
He's my nephew through marriage.
So, what happened--
did he admit to it?
- Not yet.
- Oh, damn it!
Piece of shit, man!
Fuck!
That was strange.
Have y'all noticed he's blinking
every five seconds on the dot?
What was that...
"box-top Chevy" shit?
I don't know, but I think
we might find out if we just go
to this one place on the map.
I'm telling you...
- We're not gonna do the map.
- I know.
That was my dream car
in high school.
Box-top Chevy.
And what about that rose thing?
You know, "nothing... trust
anything beautiful again"?
I used to date this girl
in high school.
My boy Pookie fucked her--
her name was Rose.
Yeah, Pookie stayed fucking her.
So...
how'd he know any of that?
I rapped about it
in some early shit.
Never released it, though.
It was on my phone.
Good cop?
Bad cop.
Devastated cop.
Oh, here they come. Okay.
I got you something.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Listen, you're obviously a fan.
And sometimes fans get excited.
And, you know, it's possible
you just took the phone
by accident,
and maybe you're embarrassed
to tell us.
- And that's fine, that happens--
- You don't have the same accent,
you know, the same
southern dialect as Paper Boi.
- Uh...
- Were you told
as a child "you talk white"?
Sometimes.
Must've made you feel separate.
What does that have
to do with anything?
Nothing, nothing.
I think it's interesting
when people aren't allowed
in the group.
The universal group.
To be "part of the team."
You know,
people just want to be seen.
Doesn't matter what for.
Can I have a cigarette?
Sure.
Here.
Cool, cool.
Why do people smoke these?
Yep, I'm done.
I'm gonna beat you right now!
Wait, wait!
I want my one phone call.
This isn't jail, Wiley.
You can call anyone at any time.
Okay, um, I don't have a phone.
Could you, could you call
a number for me?
Yeah, yeah.
So it's, um, it's 404...
And that's my fucking number,
nigga! You got my fucking phone!
- Give me my fucking phone,
man, stop playing with me!
When I'm nervous, my stomach
churns-- it's disgusting.
I am sorry.
- Please don't hurt me.
- Oh!
Hey, he's just a scared kid.
You're interrogating
a 19-year-old.
I'm 32.
Nah!
That's not strange to you?
He's not 32, no way.
He's either 32
or he's lying about being 32.
Both is strange behavior.
Has it been so long?
I-I saw him maybe 15 years ago.
- That still doesn't make him 32.
- Wait, wait.
- 15 years?
- Mm.
This guy's a stranger to you.
You don't know him at all.
He's my nephew...
through marriage.
Okay, googled his address.
It's the fucking
Cirque du Soleil headquarters.
He's toying with us.
When was the last time
you actually saw him, man?
I visited him at juvenile
offenders institute.
So jail, kid jail.
Okay, so he's in on it,
isn't he?
Hey, hey, stop, man!
Chill out, man!
Go cool your ass off, bruh.
I'm so mad,
I could kill this ni...
Oh, I'm so mad, man.
He definitely stole it.
Mm-hmm, but we ain't got
no proof.
Well, he wants
to be close to you, so...
maybe just get him to confess
and we try and record it?
Socks almost said "nigga,"
right?
- He almost called us that.
- Yeah, I heard that.
Hey, Folk, man,
can I get you to, uh...?
Uh, so how much longer do you
think you will have me detained?
Ain't nobody detaining you, man.
Okay, I-I made you a crane.
Listen,
I know things haven't gone well.
And I want to do things
the right way.
I haven't been
completely honest,
which is why you guys,
you guys, uh,
you had to resort to this, uh,
you know, this good cop,
bad cop scenario.
Uh, at this point,
I think you're probably
gonna try to, uh, record me.
To get me to say something
incriminating, but, uh...
Look, I...
I don't think
you'll get what you want
that way.
Earn, let me talk to him, man.
Check on Folk.
You know, I haven't written
anything in about...
seven months.
Seven months, man, yeah.
Like, I go to the studio,
or I lay in bed,
and like... bah.
Like, nothing comes out.
I can't find the words.
It's like I don't know
what's bad or good anymore.
You know, I was never really
into rapping, either.
Not really.
Yeah, I know, like...
now it's what I do.
It's all I do, really.
And, you know, it's just, uh,
too late
for me to do anything else.
But tonight-- oh, man-- tonight
I was out there on the dock
before the show and, uh...
I finally heard it.
I finally heard him-- my voice.
I heard him, man,
loud and clear, like...
He was singing this melody, man.
He was singing this melody
like he was a kid on a bus.
And I started singing with him,
and it was....
it was...
It was fun.
And I recorded that
on the phone.
See what I'm saying, like...?
And if I don't...
If I don't...
get it back now, then, uh...
I'm afraid I'm gonna lose it.
Forever, so...
I need that phone.
Wiley, you know what I'm saying?
Like, I need that phone.
So...
did you take my phone?
Did you know we share
a birthday?
Hmm? April 28th.
We're Tauruses.
Thank you.
He texted me to...
I like music, but I wasn't
really that into making it.
I was a lot like you.
Uh, then a girl broke my heart
in eighth grade--
her name was Rosie.
My mom moved me
and my sister to Budapest.
I was really, really, really
lonely.
But when I heard
The Postal Mixtape...
...I felt the same.
I didn't sympathize.
I didn't empathize.
I felt...
the-the same.
Um, so...
...I-I wrote this.
Thank you for seeing me.
I hope you find your phone.
Hey?
Sorry about back there, man.
Sometimes I just...
you know?
We're good, yeah?
- It's cool, man.